<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life &amp; Times</title>
    <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Life &amp; Times</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tanksuzuki&#34;&gt;Hemingway Template built by Asuka Suzuki&lt;/a&gt; 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jordancoinjackson.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case For Detroit</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/the-case-for-detroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/the-case-for-detroit/</guid>
      <description>The Case For Detroit
Detroit is in the position to take on the next generation of founders. Seriously. I’m someone who has seen the startup scene grow up close as a founder and has watched it change dramatically. I think there’s a reasonable case that can be made that Detroit should be a destination for founders more and more. Some of the most important assets a city can have to promote growth are community, economics, and culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Went From a Depressed College Dropout to a Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/how-i-went-from-a-depressed-college-dropout-to-a-software-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/how-i-went-from-a-depressed-college-dropout-to-a-software-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Life is a struggle. To happiness, to expression, to love. I’ve had my struggles too. Depression is the struggle I went through.
My alarm kept going over. BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP. I hated that noise. But I wouldn’t dare get out of bed. I remember when I was 14 and my great aunt passed away and it hit me like a ton of bricks. A feeling of hopelessness began, and school, my family situation, and being a weird kid who only stayed awake in class to watch history documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Truly Intersects</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/what_truly_intersects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/what_truly_intersects/</guid>
      <description>This is a continuation of an article I wrote here.
As well as a response to comments from a post I made from a twitter reply I made to a post about this topic.
The Social Vision Ideas have power. That power has let Liberals institute a social policy that hasn’t given the returned value for a people voting 90% Democratic. Black Americans were sold a coupled package. They received integration and fleeing white population from major cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School Is On Fire</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/the-school-is-on-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/the-school-is-on-fire/</guid>
      <description>“Where justice is denied, where poverty is enforced, where ignorance prevails, and where any one class is made to feel that society is an organized conspiracy to oppress, rob and degrade them, neither persons nor property will be safe.” ― Frederick Douglass
 In a community of the oppressed, it is a sin to discuss oppression without discussing the oppressor. To be oppressed is to be a victim. And to be an oppressor you must be the abuser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Programming &amp; Screenwriting: The Stories That Bind Us</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/programming-screenwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/programming-screenwriting/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write some questions about my experience in these two disciplines and see where and if they intersected. Here are my results so far.
When I was 18 I wrote a book of poems. When I was 19 I started my first startup. When I was 21 I wrote my first script, and now at 22 I’m building products I think can make a crucial difference in people&amp;rsquo;s lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Dragons Must Be Slain</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/all-dragons-must-be-slain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/all-dragons-must-be-slain/</guid>
      <description>All dragons must be slain. This is no play on words. From religious symbolism to medieval lore dragons are used to describe the darkest parts of ourselves, the things that keep us up late at night and has a unconscious control over our lives. But slaying the dragon is critical as it is all we should be focused on in life. The process of improving the world I believe starts with ourselves and the battles that rage right under the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness is a Process Not a Destination</title>
      <link>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/happiness-is-a-process-not-a-destination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordancoinjackson.com/blog/happiness-is-a-process-not-a-destination/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever read one of those articles on “The secrets to happiness” or “10 tips to finding happiness”? Most of them read as follows:
 What is happiness to you? Be around people that make you smile. Accept the good things in life! Be open to change.  Etc.
These tips are good — if not great if you understand what happiness actually is.
Happiness isn’t a state of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>